acgme.org 2015-06-27

# ACGME > Legal > Privacy Policy

(Last Modified: December 9, 2014)

### Introduction

**Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education** (“ **ACGME** ,” " **Company** ," or " **We** ") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website ACGME.org (our " **Website** ") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. This Privacy Policy only pertains to information collected by ACGME through this Website.

We will not share personal information gathered on this site with third parties except in limited circumstances as identified below.

We detect and use the IP address of visitors to the site in order to assist us with diagnosing and solving problems with our server and to assist with the administration of our Website.

### Changes to the Website Privacy Policy

As the Website may change from time to time, this Privacy Policy is expected to change as well. ACGME reserves the right to change this policy at any time for any reason. We will post a notice that this Privacy Policy has been amended by revising the “Last modified” date at the top of this page.

### Web Cookies

ACGME uses cookies for site navigation only. Cookies are bits of text data sent from a web server to a user's computer to be retrieved later for purposes of identification. We only use temporary cookies, which are deleted at the end of each user session. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. Consequently, your web browser is probably set to accept cookies. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to do so, however, you should understand that it is possible that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them. Unless otherwise specified, no additional information will be collected from or about you through the use of cookies.

We collect this information for statistical purposes and to make our site more useful to visitors. ACGME does not collect personal information about individual visitors nor do we supply personal or financial information about individual visitors to third parties. We also use cookies to maintain web session information to assist in site navigation. The web session cookies are deleted when the web session ends. Unless specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected from you.

We may detect and use the IP address of visitors to the site in order to assist us with diagnosing and solving problems with our server and to assist with the administration of our Website.

### Personal Information

When you browse through any website, certain information about you can be collected. Unless you input additional information via the password-protected areas of the Website, ACGME does not collect any personal information other than the information as identified below. ACGME automatically collects and temporarily stores the following information about your visit:

  * Your IP address
  * The name of the domain you use to access the Internet (for example, yahoo.com if you are using a Yahoo Online account)
  * The date, time, and length of your visit
  * The pages you visited
  * The address of the website you came from when you came to visit

In the course of site operation, personal information collected may be stored and processed in the United States. ACGME may collect, hold, and use, directly or through its affiliates, contractors, successors, assigns, and agents, the personally identifiable information you submit through the site.

ACGME may monitor, edit, or disclose your personal information, if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order). All data collected by or on behalf of ACGME relating any use of the site or its content by any users is and shall remain at all times the sole property of ACGME.

We may use the information you provide in a de-identified format as to both individual and organization, for research, quality improvement, or benchmarking purposes, and may provide this information in the aggregate to third parties. For example we might inform other users regarding the number of users to the Website.

We may contract with other companies or individuals to help us provide services, such as development or maintenance of the site. We require others to comply with the Privacy Policy and limit their access to only the information that is necessary to accomplish the task at hand and nothing more.

Unless otherwise specified above, your personal information will not be provided to any third parties.

### Security Policy

This Website has security policies and technology in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under ACGME control. This includes user personal information. We cannot, however, protect against user misuse, loss, or alteration of a user's own information. Although ACGME makes every reasonable attempt to secure your information, there is always some risk in transmitting information across the Internet. We cannot guarantee that the personal information we collect will never be disclosed in some manner not consistent with this Privacy Policy. We also cannot protect against User misuse, loss, or alteration of any user editable content.

### Contact

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, e-mail [hipaa@acgme.org.](mailto:hipaa@acgme.org)
